War brings out the beast in every man.
The Beast is a war, drama film directed by Kevin Reynolds.
During the war in Afghanistan a Soviet tank crew commanded by a tyrannical officer find themselves
lost and in a struggle against a band of Mujahadeen guerrillas in the mountains.
Daskal, played by George Dzundza.
Konstantin Koverchenko, played by Jason Patric.
Khan Taj, played by Steven Bauer.
Anthony Golikov, played by Stephen Baldwin.
Kaminski, played by Don Harvey.
Akbar, played by Kabir Bedi.
The Beast (also known as The Beast of War) is a 1988 American war film directed by Kevin
Reynolds and written by William Mastrosimone, based on his play Nənawā́te.
The film starred Jason Patric, George Dzundza, Steven Bauer,
Stephen Baldwin, Don Harvey and Erick Avari.
The film follows the crew of a Soviet T-55 tank who became
lost during the Soviet war in Afghanistan.
The film has enjoyed a cult-favorite status in spite
of its low box office statistics.
The tone is emotional.